PROPHECY TIME
There Is a woman: You have put on a pad.
It is not your period.
You have been like that for some time now.
Sometimes when you dont have money, you put on a rag,
just to stop whatever is coming out of your body.
It is no longer just blood.
Your system is damaged.
So please, come out. Jesus loves you.
You know Jesus can stop it.
Remember the woman with the issue of blood.
So come out and enjoy the grace.
In Jesus' mighty name.
Surprised by hearing her case spoken about, in the midst of a large congregation,
this lady comes forward, knowing that the solution to her embarassing problem had come.
Feeling the presence of God, she takes a deep breath
as she prepares herself for what is to come.
Man of God, I am the woman.
I'm bleeding. After my period I am still bleeding very heavily.
I'm still wearing a lot of pads because of that.
I am bleeding very heavily right now and I am not in my period.
I'm wearing a lot of pads because of that situation right now.
After the lady confirmed the prophecy to be a 100% percent true,
Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for her and deliverance begins.
In the name of Jesus Christ!
She clutches her stomach as a spiritual operation takes place.
The darkness that caused her to continually bleed is dispelled by God's great light.
Your back on the floor!
So that is the end of your bleeding.
Thank You, Jesus.
Thank You, my daughter is free.
Thank You, Jesus!
With gratitude and adoration to God, the lady's mother raises her hands to the Most High
for setting her daughter free at last,
delivering her from the burden of constant bleeding for many years.
TESTIMONY TIME
Praise the Lord!
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Bless the Lord.
My name is Lianna Douglas.
I am from Trinidad and Tobago.
Next to me are my mother Elvira Fifield and my two sisters Abigail and Shanel.
We were here last Sunday.
I was having an issue of bleeding.
Extreme bleeding.
At times it was very embarrassing for me.
When the prophecy was given by the Man of God, I was so shocked
because we had been watching Emmanuel TV for so long, seeing all these miracles.
Now I'm actually in The SCOAN and I received this prophecy.
I was stunned, I froze.
I couldn't believe it was me.
God really looked down to heal me.
When I came forward, the Man of God did not touch me.
He just pointed his hand towards me.
I felt the power of God touch my womb.
It was as though a plunger was pulling at my womb.
It was like a suction pulling at my womb.
Then, I just fell to the floor under the power of God.
Saints of God, immediately that bleeding stopped.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Since then I feel much better.
Everybody says that I look much better.
I looked at myself in the mirror and realised that I look much better. I feel better.
And I'm improving daily.
My stomach was very bulky and firm because I had multiple fibroids.
My stomach was firm and very bulky.
Since then it is very soft and pliable.
Very soft.
And now I am totally free!
Miss Lianna Douglas & Family - Prophecy Testimony
My name is Elvira Fifield.
My husband and I are pastors in the island of Trinidad and Tobago.
These are my three daughters.
We thank God for being here. Praise the Lord!
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Before we came to this country, my daughter was bleeding profusely.
It was so bad that the doctors told her that they didnt want her to travel.
Her blood count was very low.
She would be tense and nervous.
She would be palpating.
On her job, she would have problems.
The bleeding was so intense.
When we got here last Sunday, like the woman with the issue of blood, nobody knew us.
We knew no one but God saw us.
Lianna's Mother & Family - Prophecy Testimony
The Man of God called my daughter out - it had to be God.
I sat there and said, "Who knows us here, Lord? What will we do?"
But we put a demand on the anointing that was in the Man of God.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
When he made that call, it was so shocking!
I was looking forward to it but it was a unique thing.
When he made that call, I said, "Jesus, you have seen her!"
She walked to the front.
He didn't touch her.
He didn't even come close to her.
But the power of God penetrated her inner being.
When she got up and I looked at her, she said, "Mom, it is gone!"
It was the last.
It is because of the power of the Holy Ghost in the Prophet of God.
Thank God for Jesus Christ!
Thank God for a prophet who has made himself available
so that God could use him to be a blessing to the world.
Glory to God!
Thank You, Jesus.
Lianna's Mother & Family - Prophecy Testimony
No more bleeding!
It has stopped by the hand of God!
Lianna's Mother & Family - Prophecy Testimony
I came to Nigeria purposely to The SCOAN.
I thank God that He allowed us to reach here safely.
My three girls and I meant business: We were going to find this church and we are here!
Thank God for Jesus that we received more than what we came for.
Lianna's Mother & Family - Prophecy Testimony
Man of God, I would like to sing a song to thank God for what He has done for me.
Lord, how are they increased that trouble me
Many are they that rise up against me
Many there be which say of my soul,
There is no help for Her in God
But Thou, O Lord, art a shield for me
My glory, You lift mine head
My glory, the lifter up of mine head
Miss Lianna Douglas & Family - Prophecy Testimony
Thank you.